# **Mahmoud Badwy**

# Software Developer

mahmoud-badwy k my-portfolio

## **Personal information**

I'm Mahmoud Badwy, Mobile app developer With 2 years of experience in mobile app development and a thorough understanding of Flutter, Dart, and Android app development, I am confident in my ability to deliver high-quality work within the given timeframe.

## **Professional Experience**

02/2022 - 12/2022 Flutter Developer, Alex Apps □ Flutter internship Alexandria, Egypt

**IT Technical,** *GDGDamanhour* □ 01/2023 - present

Damanhour, Egypt

**Mobile App Contect Creator,** Front-End Capsules ☑ 01/2023 - present

Flutter Developer, Magia 🗷 present

Alexandria, Egypt

#### **Skills**

**Flutter Dart** 

OOP Java

**SOLID Clean Architecture** 

Clean Architecture, MVVM, MVC

Api

HTTP, Dio **State Management** 

Provider, GetX

**Database** 

Sql, No Sql Sql

**Local Databases Flutter Animation** 

Shared preferences, Sqflite, Hive Tween, Animation Controller, others

**Clean Code** 

Authentication, Firestore, Realtime, Firebase Storage

## **Projects**

Mix Video ♂

Anime, Film and Manga videos app

Dating App 🖸

Social Media App

Student Home 🛮

**Educational App** 

Make it ☑ ToDo List App

Qr Mirror

Qr code reader and generater

# Languages

• Arabic

• English

• Turkish

• French